{
    "subject": "Eddie_Griffin",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Dysfunktional_Family",
    "human_readable": "Eddie Griffin acted in Dysfunktional Family.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9880563020706177,
            "question": "What role did Eddie Griffin play in Dysfunktional Family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8555219173431396,
            "question": "Which actor starred in Dysfunktional Family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6064347624778748,
            "question": "Is Eddie Griffin known for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5441710352897644,
            "question": "Was Dysfunktional Family a successful movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3651896119117737,
            "question": "What genre of film is Dysfunktional Family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35021352767944336,
            "question": "What movie did Eddie Griffin act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34251028299331665,
            "question": "Name a movie starring Eddie Griffin."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3356172442436218,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Eddie Griffin's acting career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3339771330356598,
            "question": "In what film did Eddie Griffin star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2318734973669052,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie featuring Eddie Griffin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eddie Griffin acted in Dysfunktional Family.",
            "html": "yago_29790_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what film did Eddie Griffin star?",
            "html": "yago_29790_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Eddie Griffin's acting career?",
            "html": "yago_29790_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a movie starring Eddie Griffin.",
            "html": "yago_29790_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_141.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_161.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_29790_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Eddie Griffin acted in Dysfunktional Family. The documents mention that Dysfunktional Family is a concert performance featuring Eddie Griffin, and also include behind-the-scenes documentary footage detailing his personal life and family."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Eddie Griffin acted in Dysfunktional Family.\" The first and third document entries explicitly state that Dysfunktional Family is a film starring Eddie Griffin, and the fifth document entry mentions Eddie Griffin's performance in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}